{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Landscape Designers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/40025/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40025,"taskName":"Designer - Landscape","taskDescription":"Landscape Designer","xmTaskDescriptor":"Landscape Designers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":282,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"landscape landscaping xeroscape xeriscaping design","textMessagingName":"Landscape Design","rolloverLongDesc":"These professionals lack the credentials of landscape architects, but holds themselves out as experts in designing landscaping projects.","rolloverShortDesc":"Non-credentialed designer of landscapes.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Landscape Designer.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Landscape Designers \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Home \u0026 Curb Landscape Design","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Landscape Designer","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Designer - Landscape","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Landscape Designer Need","urlName":"Designer-Landscape","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Landscape Designers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"landscape,landscaping,xeroscape,xeriscaping,design,hardscape,hardscaping,garden","emcCategoryOid":-12019,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":349,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40025/":{"taskOID":40025,"originalTaskOID":40025,"setID":349,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4834,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this landscaping project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4169,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New landscape from bare dirt","answerDisplayText":"New landscape from bare dirt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5298,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Completely replace existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6617,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Updating existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Updating existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4837,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which areas of your yard do you want to be designed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3014,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hillside","answerDisplayText":"Hillside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4839,"questionDisplayText":"Who will install?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who will install the landscaping?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11231,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Will hire contractor to install ","answerDisplayText":"Will hire contractor to install ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11232,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Homeowner will install ","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner will install ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7186,"questionDisplayText":"What is the approximate size of the area to be landscaped?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of the area to be landscaped?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11227,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11228,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11229,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11230,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4834,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this landscaping project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4169,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New landscape from bare dirt","answerDisplayText":"New landscape from bare dirt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5298,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Completely replace existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6617,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Updating existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Updating existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4169,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New landscape from bare dirt","answerDisplayText":"New landscape from bare dirt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5298,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Completely replace existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6617,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Updating existing landscape","answerDisplayText":"Updating existing landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4837,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which areas of your yard do you want to be designed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3014,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hillside","answerDisplayText":"Hillside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3014,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hillside","answerDisplayText":"Hillside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4839,"questionDisplayText":"Who will install?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who will install the landscaping?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11231,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Will hire contractor to install ","answerDisplayText":"Will hire contractor to install ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11232,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Homeowner will install ","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner will install ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11231,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Will hire contractor to install ","answerDisplayText":"Will hire contractor to install ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11232,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Homeowner will install ","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner will install ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7186,"questionDisplayText":"What is the approximate size of the area to be landscaped?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of the area to be landscaped?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11227,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11228,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11229,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11230,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11227,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11228,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11229,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11230,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft) ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}